

CONTACT



+598-98-158-899



axel.lavignasse@gmail.com



Uruguay, Montevideo

SKILLs

Javascript

CSS

.....

SASS

Soft Skills - Communication

Git

JQuery

....

Bootstrap

GitHub

PORTFOLIO

https://axellancieri.github.io/

Axel Lancieri

Proactive self learning individual, 7 years of experience working first hand helping customers working on my soft skills, empathy and problem solving skills.

Studying a career as a Front End Web Developer, certified by the <u>Treehouse Techdegree</u> where I developed and designed a portfolio showcasing all of my projects.

EXPERIENCE

Retail / Product Support Specialist

2016-2022

Alorica

Offered customer service all abroad the world on a massive retail company that's a client of Alorica. Started as a retail employee providing customer support related to bank authorizations, logistics, promotions and promoted services based on yearly themes. Later on I moved to a more specialized team where I offered product support on items bought by customers of any type and sort, my job was to help the customer troubleshoot the item exercising problem solving skills and if the issue was outside of the scope, then make sure the customer gets a good resolution and has a great overall experience.

Attendant

2014-2015

Puerta del Sur

Based on the availability and the traffic at the airport I would work helping customers get through the check-in process, I was posted on the first security line where I would double check their passports and the flight ticket to make sure everything checks out and they can move forward on the check-in procedure, otherwise I would be on the parking lot taking offering various services such as a cashier on the parking tickets or private flights taxes, valet-parking and different parking lot promotions.

EDUCATION

Currently learning React.js

2023

Treehouse, CA

Personal References

Ignacio Picun – Lead Front-End Dev \$\displays +598-98-158-899

Front End Web Developer Techdegree

2021-2022

Treehouse, CA

All my current portfolio work has been done during this course.

Highschool

2015

Liceo n10 Montevideo, Uruguay

Graduated with an orientation on medicine.